// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
//MEDIUM CSS

let questions = [


{
    numb:1,
    question:"What type of CSS is generally recommended for designing large web pages?",
    answer:"B. External",
    options:[
    "A. Inline",
    "B. External",
    "C. Internal",
    "D.None of the above",
    ]
},

{ 
    numb:2,
    question:"How can we select an element with a specific ID in CSS?",
    answer:"A. #",
    options:[
    "A. #",
    "B. .",
    "C. ^",
    "D. None of the above",
    ]
},

{ 
    numb:3,
    question:"Can negtive values be allowed in padding property?",
    answer:"B. No",
    options:[
    "A. Yes",
    "B. No",
    "C. Depends on Property",
    "D. None of the above",
    ]
},

{
    numb:4,
    question:"How can we specify the spacing between each letter of an element?",
    answer:"B. letter-spacing",
    options:[
    "A. alpha-spacing",
    "B. letter-spacing",
    "C. character-spacing",
    "D. None of the above",
    ]
},

{
    numb:5,
    question:"We can make rounded borders around elements using which CSS element?",
    answer:"C. border-radius",
    options:[
    "A. border-collapse",
    "B. border-round",
    "C. border-radius",
    "D. None of the above",
    ]   
},

{
    numb:6,
    question:"How can we set the maximum width of the elements content box using CSS?",
    answer:"C. max-width property",
    options:[
    "A. height property",
    "B. max-height property",
    "C. max-width property",
    "D.None of the above",
    ]
},

{
    numb:7,
    question:"How can we select an element with a specific Class in CSS?",
    answer:"B. .",
    options:[
    "A. #",
    "B. .",
    "C. ^",
    "D. None of the above",
    ]
},

{
    numb:8,
    question:"Which CSS property is used to create an image reflection?",
    answer:"A. box-reflect",
    options:[
    "A. box-reflect",
    "B. image-reflect",
    "C. reflect-img",
    "D. None of the above",
    ]
},

{
    numb:9,
    question:'Which of the following are units of relative length in CSS?',
    answer:"D. All the above",
    options:[
    "A. em",
    "B. rem",
    "C. vmax",
    "D. All the above",
    ]
},

{ 
    numb:10,
    question:"How can we select elements with a specified attribute in CSS?",
    answer:"A. [attribute] selector",
    options:[
    "A. [attribute] selector",
    "B. [property] selector",
    "C. Both A and B",
    "D. None of the above",
    ]
},

{
    numb:11,
    question:"true or False: CSS is primarily resonsible for handling server-side logic in web applications?",
    answer:"B. False",
    options:[
    "A. True",
    "B. False",
    ]
},

{
    numb:12,
    question:"Which CSS selector is denoted by a dot followed by the class name?",
    answer:"C. Class selector",
    options:[
    "A. Universal selector",
    "B. ID selector",
    "C. Class selector",
    "D. Element selector",
    ]
},

{
    numb:13,
    question:"Which CSS type is applied directly to the HTML element using the style attribute?",
    answer:"A. Inline CSS",
    options:[
    "A. Inline CSS",
    "B. Internal CSS",
    "C. External CSS",
    "D. Embedded CSS",
    ]
},

{
    numb:14,
    question:"Which input typr is used for collecting multiple-choice responses from users?",
    answer:"C. checkbox",
    options:[
    "A. text",
    "B. radio",
    "C. ckeckbox",
    "D. password",
    ]
},

{
    numb:15,
    question:"Which CSS property is used to position an element relative to its normal position?",
    answer:"D. position:relative",
    options:[
    "A. position:absolute",
    "B. position:fixed",
    "C. position:static",
    "D. position:relative",
    ]
},
    



  
];